const example = [
  {
    category: "Entertainment%3A%20Books",
    type: "multiple",
    difficulty: "easy",
    question: "Who%20wrote%20%22Harry%20Potter%22%3F",
    correct_answer: "J.K.%20Rowling",
    incorrect_answers: [
      "J.R.R.%20Tolkien",
      "Terry%20Pratchett",
      "Daniel%20Radcliffe",
    ],
  },
  {
    category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
    type: "multiple",
    difficulty: "hard",
    question:
      "What%20was%20the%20name%20of%20the%20hero%20in%20the%2080s%20animated%20video%20game%20%27Dragon%27s%20Lair%27%3F",
    correct_answer: "Dirk%20the%20Daring",
    incorrect_answers: ["Arthur", "Sir%20Toby%20Belch", "Guy%20of%20Gisbourne"],
  },
  {
    category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
    type: "multiple",
    difficulty: "medium",
    question:
      "What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20currency%20in%20the%20%22Animal%20Crossing%22%20series%3F",
    correct_answer: "Bells",
    incorrect_answers: ["Sea%20Shells", "Leaves", "Bugs"],
  },
  {
    category: "Entertainment%3A%20Board%20Games",
    type: "multiple",
    difficulty: "medium",
    question:
      "How%20many%20points%20is%20the%20Z%20tile%20worth%20in%20Scrabble%3F",
    correct_answer: "10",
    incorrect_answers: ["8", "5", "6"],
  },
  {
    category: "Science%3A%20Gadgets",
    type: "multiple",
    difficulty: "hard",
    question:
      "Which%20of%20the%20following%20cellular%20device%20companies%20is%20NOT%20headquartered%20in%20Asia%3F",
    correct_answer: "Nokia",
    incorrect_answers: ["LG%20Electronics", "Samsung", "HTC"],
  },
  {
    category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
    type: "multiple",
    difficulty: "medium",
    question:
      "Who%20developed%20the%202016%20farming%20RPG%20%22Stardew%20Valley%22%3F",
    correct_answer: "Eric%20Barone",
    incorrect_answers: ["Daisuke%20Amaya", "Jasper%20Byrne", "Lucas%20Pope"],
  },
  {
    category: "Science%20%26%20Nature",
    type: "multiple",
    difficulty: "medium",
    question: "The%20Sun%20consists%20of%20mostly%20which%20two%20elements%3F",
    correct_answer: "Hydrogen%20%26%20Helium",
    incorrect_answers: [
      "Hydrogen%20%26%20Nitrogen",
      "Carbon%20%26%20Nitrogen",
      "Carbon%20%26%20Helium",
    ],
  },
  {
    category: "History",
    type: "multiple",
    difficulty: "medium",
    question:
      "Which%20of%20the%20following%20Presidents%20of%20the%20United%20States%20was%20assassinated%3F",
    correct_answer: "William%20McKinley",
    incorrect_answers: [
      "Lyndon%20Johnson",
      "Chester%20Arthur",
      "Franklin%20Roosevelt",
    ],
  },
  {
    category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
    type: "multiple",
    difficulty: "medium",
    question:
      "In%20Need%20for%20Speed%3A%20Underground%2C%20what%20car%20does%20Eddie%20drive%3F",
    correct_answer: "Nissan%20Skyline%20GT-R%20%28R34%29",
    incorrect_answers: [
      "Mazda%20RX-7%20FD3S",
      "Acura%20Integra%20Type%20R",
      "Subaru%20Impreza%202.5%20RS",
    ],
  },
  {
    category: "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
    type: "multiple",
    difficulty: "easy",
    question:
      "Before%20it%27s%20redesign%20of%20the%20company%20logo%20in%20the%20year%202000%2C%20which%203D%20shape%20is%20NOT%20represented%20in%20the%20Electronic%20Arts%20logo%3F",
    correct_answer: "Cylinder",
    incorrect_answers: ["Pyramid", "Cube", "Sphere"],
  },
];

export default example;
